devot-ee.com 2016-10-23

# Privacy Policy - devot:ee - Devoted to ExpressionEngine

##  Privacy

###  devot:ee Respects your Online Privacy

This is devot:ee’s online privacy policy. Thank you for visiting devot:ee ("devot:ee"), located online at: http://devot-ee.com ("Site"). We respect the privacy of our customers, partners, and clients, and take your privacy very seriously.

####  Personal Information Gathering and Use

We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. devot:ee asks that customers supply certain personal data when registering and placing orders, including name, physical address, email address, and credit card information. This data is used only for the purpose of fulfilling orders or communicating with customers, or partners (such as add-on developers) regarding orders. Guests may browse devot-ee.com for free, without having to enter or supply any personal information.

####  Cookies

Like many other websites, devot:ee may use "cookies" (small text files stored locally on your machine) that allow us to customize your visit, or help us track your access to restricted areas (for those registered users). Cookies are used with discretion, and do not contain any personal or sensitive information.

####  Sharing Personal Information

devot:ee may share your personal information with partners or suppliers in order for them to fulfill the service or product you have ordered. This may include the maker or provider of the product you have purchased, companies used to process credit card or other payment types, deliver packages, provide customer service, or otherwise provide services that enable us to serve you. These organizations will have access only to the information required to permit them to perform their obligations to us. We make order information available to add-on developers through an API so that they are better able to support you after having purchased their item(s), which may include your name, email, and company name. For complete information on what is shared in our Orders API, see the API documentation.

Beyond these mentioned disclosures, we will only disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority, to prevent harm to yourself or others, or to protect against fraud. We may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which devot:ee participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of devot:ee’s assets. Such successor entity shall be bound by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.

####  Links to Third Party Sites

This Site may be linked to other web sites on the Internet which are not under the control of or maintained by devot:ee. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by devot:ee of those other web sites, the content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith. You acknowledge that devot:ee is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and you agree that devot:ee is not responsible for the content of such sites. Your use of these other linked web sites is subject to the respective terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked sites.

####  Security

devot:ee employs procedural and technological measures, consistent with the demands of customer service. Such measures are reasonably designed to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Where reasonably practical, devot:ee uses SSL and other encryption, password protection, internal restrictions and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

####  Updating Your Information

If you wish to update your personally identifiable information you may do so any time on your main member page while you are logged into the site.

####  Policy Changes

devot:ee reserves the right to change this privacy policy, and will post any revisions on its website located at http://devot-ee.com. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this web site will be subject to the then-current privacy policy.

If you have questions or comments regarding devot:ee’s privacy practices you can contact us at: Masuga Design, LLC d/b/a devot:ee, 648 Monroe Ave. NW, Suite 105, Grand Rapids, MI 49503 or contact us via [email](mailto:ryan@devot-ee.com).
